Luis Enrique Vega Martinez

Frontend Developer

Cartagena, Colombia (UTC-5) (+57) 301 794 3503 luisevegam.91@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/luisenriquevegamartinez https://github.com/LuisVega91

Frontend Developer with +4 years of experience with Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, Nodels and familiarity with frameworks such as NestlS, Express and React. I had the opportunity to implement an architecture based on micro-frontends using (Module Federation), and I have used all the tools provided by angular. I am looking for a remote full-time job.

EXPERIENCE

Parallel Staff, Frontend Developer — February 2023 - May 2023

- Successfully developed 100% of the frontend for a new feature called "incremental campaign rollout" on the administration portal, allowing for progressive updates by device groups and improving the efficiency of the portal in
- Reduced the number of UI errors present in the 1.13 project release to 0% by proactively identifying and solving
- Successfully updated the UI frameworks from Angular 13 to Angular 15 in all frontend repositories, improving the overall functionality and performance of the system.

Tech Stack: Angular, Angular Material, Bootstrap 3, 4 and 5, NgBoostrap, Git, GitLab, Jenkins, karma, Jasmine.

Sophos Solutions S A S, Solution Consultant I

FullStack - Plink (Bancolombia) — March 2022- February 2023

- Migration of 10 endpoints from javascript to typescript using clean architectures and microservices,
- Refactorization applying the best practices, and SOLID principles in 100% of endpoints migrated.
- Develop unit tests of 100% of migrated endpoints with 100% code coverage.

Tech Stack: Angular, Node.js, Express.js, TypeScript, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, AWS, Git, Jest, Sequelize.

- Frontend Mi Cuenta Su + (Intercredito) October 2021 March 2022

 Implemented an architecture based on Micro-frontends that assimilated 100% of the project's modules.
 - Developed a node S script to automate the build of each micro-frontend during the deployment process.
 - Reduced the time to add micro-frontends from 2h to 1m by creating a nodeJS script to automate the steps.

Tech Stack: Angular, Angular Material, Module Federation, Docker, Jest, Git, Postgres.

Cinte Colombia, Frontend Developer — Abril 2021 - October 2021

- Reduced the time to add new features from 2h to 1m by building a nodejs script to automate the creation of new modules in the architecture of the Claro Inspira project.
- Developed 100% of components and services of Parametrizations module of Claro Inspira project.
- Developed unit tests of 100% of developed components and services with 100% code coverage of the Claro Inspira

Tech Stack: Angular, Redux (NGRX), Angular Material, Git.

Escuela Taller Cartagena De Indias, Software Developer — July 2020 - December 2020

- Developed frontend modules that collected all purchases and sales modes of San Felipe Castle tickets.
- Developed the frontend modules of San Felipe Castle ERP. https://compraenlinea.fortificacionescartagena.com.co.
- Promoted the current reservation flow, improving the security, and reducing the probability of sabotage.

Tech stack: Angular, Ionic, Git, rxjs.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Advanced: JavaScript, TypeScript; Intermediate: Dart; Basic: C#. Frameworks Tools: Advanced: Angular; Intermediate: Express, NestJs, React, Flutter; Basic: .Net. Data Base: Intermediate: PostgreSQL, MySQL; Intermediate: Mongo, Firebase; Basic: SQL Server.

Tools: VSTS, Figma. Agile: SCRUM.

Languages: Intermediate: English; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

Universidad del Sinú Elías Bechara Zainúm - Cartagena Bolívar. Bachelor's Degree, Systems Engineering, December 2016. Servicio Educativo Nacional SENA – Cartagena Bolívar. Associate's Degree, Computer Network Administration, December 2012.

CERTIFICATIONS

.NET Entity Framework Core esencial – Linkedin learning. 2022 .NET 6 esencial – Linkedin learning. 2022. Conceptos Básicos de DevOps – SP Academy. 2022 DevOps con Azure DevOps - nivel básico – SP Academy. 2022.